A Guide to the Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads, 1899-1975
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads, 1899-1975., Extent: 366 boxes; 165 cubic feet. (Box 1-366)
  - 1917.
    - Southern, 1917 (Box 110)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1917 (Box 110)
    - Tazewell Street, 1917 (Box 110)
    - Valley, 1917 (Box 110)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1917 (Box 110)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1917 (Box 110)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1917 (Box 110)
    - Virginian, 1917 (Box 110)
    - Virginian Terminal (3 folders), 1917 (Box 110)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1917 (Box 111)
    - Virginia Southern, 1917 (Box 111)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1917 (Box 111)
    - Washington - Virginia, 1917 (Box 111)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1917 (Box 111)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1917 (Box 111)
  - 1918.
    - Appalachian Power Company, 1918 (Box 111)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1918 (Box 111)
    - Atlantic Coast Line (2 folders), 1918 (Box 111)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1918 (Box 112)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio (2 folders), 1918 (Box 112)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1918 (Box 112)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio (2 folders), 1918 (Box 112)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1918 (Box 112)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1918 (Box 112)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1918 (Box 112)
    - Danville and Western (2 folders), 1918 (Box 113)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1918 (Box 113)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1918 (Box 113)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1918 (Box 113)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1918 (Box 113)
    - Interstate, 1918 (Box 113)
    - Laurel, 1918 (Box 113)
    - Louisville and Nashville (2 folders), 1918 (Box 113)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1918 (Box 113)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1918 (Box 114)
    - Mill Mountain Incline Incorporated, 1918 (Box 114)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1918 (Box 114)
    - Newport News and Hampton Railway, Gas, and Electric Company, 1918 (Box 114)
    - New River, Holston, and Western (2 folders), 1918 (Box 114)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk (2 folders), 1918 (Box 114)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line (2 folders), 1918 (Box 114)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1918 (Box 115)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1918 (Box 115)
    - Norfolk Southern (2 folders), 1918 (Box 115)
    - Norfolk Terminal (2 folders), 1918 (Box 115)
    - Norton and Northern, 1918 (Box 115)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1918 (Box 115)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1918 (Box 115)
    - Radford Water Power Company, 1918 (Box 115)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac (2 folders), 1918 (Box 116)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg, 1918 (Box 116)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg (2 folders), 1918 (Box 116)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1918 (Box 116)
    - Roaring Fork (2 folders), 1918 (Box 116)
    - Rosslyn Connecting (2 folders), 1918 (Box 116)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1918 (Box 116)
    - Seven Pines, 1918 (Box 117)
    - Shenandoah Traction Company, 1918 (Box 117)
    - Southern (2 folders), 1918 (Box 117)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1918 (Box 117)
    - Tazewell Street, 1918 (Box 117)
    - Valley (2 folders), 1918 (Box 117)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1918 (Box 117)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1918 (Box 117)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1918 (Box 117)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1918 (Box 118)
    - Virginian (2 folders), 1918 (Box 118)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1918 (Box 118)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1918 (Box 118)
    - Virginia Southern, 1918 (Box 118)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1918 (Box 118)
    - Washington Southern (2 folders), 1918 (Box 118)
    - Washington - Virginia, 1918 (Box 118)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1918 (Box 118)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1918 (Box 119)
    - Winchester and Strasburg (2 folders), 1918 (Box 119)
  - 1919.
    - Appalachian Power Company, 1919 (Box 119)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1919 (Box 119)
    - Atlantic Coast Line (2 folders), 1919 (Box 119)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1919 (Box 119)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio (2 folders), 1919 (Box 119)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1919 (Box 120)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio (2 folders), 1919 (Box 120)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1919 (Box 120)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1919 (Box 120)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg (2 folders), 1919 (Box 120)
    - Danville and Western, 1919 (Box 120)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1919 (Box 120)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1919 (Box 120)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1919 (Box 121)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1919 (Box 121)
    - Interstate, 1919 (Box 121)
    - Laurel, 1919 (Box 121)
    - Louisville and Nashville (2 folders), 1919 (Box 121)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1919 (Box 121)
    - Marion and Rye Company, 1919 (Box 121)
    - Mill Mountain Incline Company, 1919 (Box 121)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1919 (Box 121)
    - Newport News and Hampton Railroad, Gas and Electric Company, 1919 (Box 122)
    - New River, Holston, and Western (2 folders), 1919 (Box 122)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk (2 folders), 1919 (Box 122)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line (2 folders), 1919 (Box 122)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1919 (Box 122)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1919 (Box 122)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1919 (Box 122)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1919 (Box 123)
    - Norfolk Terminal (2 folders), 1919 (Box 123)
    - Norton and Northern, 1919 (Box 123)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point (2 folders), 1919 (Box 123)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont (2 folders), 1919 (Box 123)
    - Radford Water Power Company, 1919 (Box 123)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac (2 folders), 1919 (Box 123)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg, 1919 (Box 123)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1919 (Box 123)
    - Richmond Terminal (2 folders), 1919 (Box 124)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1919 (Box 124)
    - Roaring Fork, 1919 (Box 124)
    - Rosslyn Connecting (2 folders), 1919 (Box 124)
    - Seaboard Air Line (2 folders), 1919 (Box 124)
    - Seven Pines, 1919 (Box 124)
    - Southern, 1919 (Box 124)
    - Shenandoah Traction Company, 1919 (Box 125)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1919 (Box 125)
    - Tazewell Street 1919 (Box 125)
    - Valley (2 folders), 1919 (Box 125)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1919 (Box 125)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1919 (Box 125)
    - Virginia - Carolina (2 folders), 1919 (Box 125)
    - Virginian (2 folders), 1919 (Box 125)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1919 (Box 126)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1919 (Box 126)
    - Virginia Southern, 1919 (Box 126)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1919 (Box 126)
    - Washington and Southern (2 folders), 1919 (Box 126)
    - Washington - Virginia, 1919 (Box 126)
    - Winchester and Potomac (2 folders), 1919 (Box 126)
    - Winchester and Strasburg (2 folders), 1919 (Box 126)
  - 1920.
    - American Railway Express Company, 1920 (Box 127)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1920 (Box 127)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1920 (Box 127)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1920 (Box 127)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1920 (Box 127)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1920 (Box 127)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1920 (Box 127)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1920 (Box 127)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1920 (Box 128)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1920 (Box 128)
    - Danville and Western, 1920 (Box 128)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1920 (Box 128)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1920 (Box 128)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1920 (Box 128)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1920 (Box 128)
    - Interstate, 1920 (Box 128)
    - Laurel, 1920 (Box 128)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1920 (Box 128)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1920 (Box 128)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1920 (Box 129)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1920 (Box 129)
    - Newport News and Hampton Railway, Gas and Electric Company, 1920 (Box 129)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1920 (Box 129)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1920 (Box 129)
    - Norfolk and Western (2 folders), 1920 (Box 129)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1920 (Box 129)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1920 (Box 129)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1920 (Box 129)
    - Norton and Northern, 1920 (Box 130)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1920 (Box 130)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1920 (Box 130)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1920 (Box 130)
    - Rapidan, 1920 (Box 130)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1920 (Box 130)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1920 (Box 130)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1920 (Box 130)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1920 (Box 130)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1920 (Box 130)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1920 (Box 131)
    - Roaring Fork, 1920 (Box 131)
    - Rossyln Crossing, 1920 (Box 131)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1920 (Box 131)
    - Shenandoah Traction Company, 1920 (Box 131)
    - Southern, 1920 (Box 131)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1920 (Box 131)
    - Tazewell Street, 1920 (Box 131)
    - Valley, 1920 (Box 131)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1920 (Box 131)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1920 (Box 131)
    - Virginian, 1920 (Box 132)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1920 (Box 132)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1920 (Box 132)
    - Virginia Southern, 1920 (Box 132)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1920 (Box 132)
    - Washington Southern, 1920 (Box 132)
    - Washington - Virginia, 1920 (Box 132)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1920 (Box 132)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1920 (Box 132)
  - 1921.
    - American Railway Express Company, 1921 (Box 132)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1921 (Box 133)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1921 (Box 133)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1921 (Box 133)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1921 (Box 133)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1921 (Box 133)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1921 (Box 133)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1921 (Box 133)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1921 (Box 134)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1921 (Box 134)
    - Danville and Western, 1921 (Box 134)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1921 (Box 134)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1921 (Box 134)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1921 (Box 134)
    - Interstate, 1921 (Box 134)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1921 (Box 134)
    - Lynchburg and Nashville, 1921 (Box 134)
    - Lynchburg Traction Light Company, 1921 (Box 134)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1921 (Box 134)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1921 (Box 134)
    - Newport News and Hampton Railway, Gas, and Electric Company, 1921 (Box 135)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1921 (Box 135)
    - Norfolk and Portsmough Belt Line, 1921 (Box 135)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1921 (Box 135)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1921 (Box 135)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1921 (Box 135)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1921 (Box 135)
    - Norton and Northern, 1921 (Box 135)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1921 (Box 136)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1921 (Box 136)
    - Princeton, 1921 (Box 136)
    - Radford Water Power Company, 1921 (Box 136)
    - Rapidan, 1921 (Box 136)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1921 (Box 136)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1921 (Box 136)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1921 (Box 136)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1921 (Box 136)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1921 (Box 136)
    - Roanoke, 1921 (Box 136)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1921 (Box 137)
    - Roaring Fork, 1921 (Box 137)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1921 (Box 137)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1921 (Box 137)
    - Shenandoah Traction Company, 1921 (Box 137)
    - Southeastern Express Company, 1921 (Box 137)
    - Southern, 1921 (Box 137)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1921 (Box 137)
    - Tazewell Street, 1921 (Box 137)
    - Valley, 1921 (Box 137)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1921 (Box 138)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1921 (Box 138)
    - Virginian, 1921 (Box 138)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1921 (Box 138)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1921 (Box 138)
    - Virginia Southern, 1921 (Box 138)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1921 (Box 138)
    - Washington - Virginia, 1921 (Box 138)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1921 (Box 138)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1921 (Box 138)
  - 1922.
    - American Railway Express Company, 1922 (Box 139)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1922 (Box 139)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1922 (Box 139)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1922 (Box 139)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1922 (Box 139)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1922 (Box 139)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1922 (Box 139)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1922 (Box 139)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1922 (Box 140)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1922 (Box 140)
    - Danville and Western, 1922 (Box 140)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1922 (Box 140)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1922 (Box 140)
    - Interstate, 1922 (Box 140)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1922 (Box 140)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1922 (Box 140)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1922 (Box 140)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1922 (Box 140)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1922 (Box 141)
    - Newport News and Hampton Railway, Gas, and Electric Company, 1922 (Box 141)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1922 (Box 141)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1922 (Box 141)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company 1922 (Box 141)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1922 (Box 141)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1922 (Box 141)
    - Norton and Northern, 1922 (Box 141)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1922 (Box 141)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1922 (Box 141)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1922 (Box 142)
    - Rapidan, 1922 (Box 142)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1922 (Box 142)
    - Richmond and Petersburg, 1922 (Box 142)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1922 (Box 142)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1922 (Box 142)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1922 (Box 142)
    - Roanoke, 1922 (Box 142)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1922 (Box 142)
    - Roaring Fork, 1922 (Box 142)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1922 (Box 142)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1922 (Box 143)
    - Shenandoah Traction Company, 1922 (Box 143)
    - Southeastern Express Company, 1922 (Box 143)
    - Southern, 1922 (Box 143)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1922 (Box 143)
    - Tazewell Street, 1922 (Box 143)
    - Valley, 1922 (Box 143)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1922 (Box 143)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1922 (Box 143)
    - Virginian, 1922 (Box 143)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1922 (Box 144)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1922 (Box 144)
    - Virginia Southern, 1922 (Box 144)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1922 (Box 144)
    - Washington - Virginia, 1922 (Box 144)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1922 (Box 144)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1922 (Box 144)
  - 1923.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1923 (Box 144)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1923 (Box 144)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1923 (Box 144)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1923 (Box 145)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1923 (Box 145)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1923 (Box 145)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1923 (Box 145)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1923 (Box 145)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1923 (Box 145)
    - Danville and Western, 1923 (Box 145)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1923 (Box 145)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1923 (Box 145)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1923 (Box 146)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1923 (Box 146)
    - Interstate, 1923 (Box 146)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1923 (Box 146)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1923 (Box 146)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1923 (Box 146)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1923 (Box 146)
    - Newport News and Hampton Railroad, Gas, and Electric, 1923 (Box 146)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1923 (Box 146)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1923 (Box 147)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1923 (Box 147)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1923 (Box 147)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1923 (Box 147)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1923 (Box 147)
    - Norton and Northern, 1923 (Box 147)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1923 (Box 147)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1923 (Box 147)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1923 (Box 147)
    - Rapidan, 1923 (Box 148)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1923 (Box 148)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1923 (Box 148)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1923 (Box 148)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1923 (Box 148)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1923 (Box 148)
    - Roanoke, 1923 (Box 148)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1923 (Box 148)
    - Roaring Fork, 1923 (Box 148)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1923 (Box 148)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1923 (Box 149)
    - Shenandoah Traction Company, 1923 (Box 149)
    - Southern, 1923 (Box 149)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1923 (Box 149)
    - Tazewell Street 1923 (Box 149)
    - Valley, 1923 (Box 149)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1923 (Box 149)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1923 (Box 149)
    - Virginian, 1923 (Box 149)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1923 (Box 150)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1923 (Box 150)
    - Virginia Southern, 1923 (Box 150)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1923 (Box 150)
    - Washington - Virginia, 1923 (Box 150)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1923 (Box 150)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1923 (Box 150)
  - 1924.
    - American Railway Express, 1924 (Box 150)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1924 (Box 150)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1924 (Box 151)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1924 (Box 150)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1924 (Box 150)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1924 (Box 150)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1924 (Box 151)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1924 (Box 151)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1924 (Box 151)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1924 (Box 151)
    - Danville and Western, 1924 (Box 152)
    - Danville Traction and Power, 1924 (Box 152)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1924 (Box 152)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1924 (Box 152)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1924 (Box 152)
    - Interstate, 1924 (Box 152)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1924 (Box 152)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light, 1924 (Box 152)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1924 (Box 152)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1924 (Box 152)
    - Newport News and Hampton Railway, Gas and Electric Company, 1924 (Box 153)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1924 (Box 153)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1924 (Box 153)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1924 (Box 153)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1924 (Box 153)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1924 (Box 153)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1924 (Box 153)
    - Norton and Northern, 1924 (Box 153)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1924 (Box 153)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1924 (Box 153)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1924 (Box 154)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1924 (Box 154)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1924 (Box 154)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1924 (Box 154)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1924 (Box 154)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1924 (Box 154)
    - Roanoke, 1924 (Box 154)
    - Roanoke Railroad and Electric Company, 1924 (Box 154)
    - Roaring Fork, 1924 (Box 154)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1924 (Box 154)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1924 (Box 155)
    - Shenandoah Traction Company, 1924 (Box 155)
    - Southeastern Express Company, 1924 (Box 155)
    - Southern, 1924 (Box 155)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1924 (Box 155)
    - Tazewell Street, 1924 (Box 155)
    - Valley, 1924 (Box 155)
    - Virginia and Southeastern, 1924 (Box 155)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1924 (Box 155)
    - Virginian, 1924 (Box 156)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1924 (Box 156)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1924 (Box 156)
    - Virginia Southern, 1924 (Box 156)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1924 (Box 156)
    - Washington - Virginia, 1924 (Box 156)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1924 (Box 156)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1924 (Box 156)
    - Winchester and Western, 1924 (Box 156)
  - 1925.
    - American Railway Express Company, 1925 (Box 157)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1925 (Box 157)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1925 (Box 157)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1925 (Box 157)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1925 (Box 157)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1925 (Box 157)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1925 (Box 157)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1925 (Box 157)
    - Clinchfield, 1925 (Box 157)
    - Cumberland and Martinsburg, 1925 (Box 158)
    - Danville and Western, 1925 (Box 158)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1925 (Box 158)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1925 (Box 158)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1925 (Box 158)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1925 (Box 158)
    - Interstate, 1925 (Box 158)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1925 (Box 158)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1925 (Box 158)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1925 (Box 158)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1925 (Box 159)
    - Newport News and Hampton Railway, Gas and Electric, 1925 (Box 159)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1925 (Box 159)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1925 (Box 159)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1925 (Box 159)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1925 (Box 159)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1925 (Box 159)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1925 (Box 159)
    - Norton and Northern, 1925 (Box 159)
    - Orange and Fredericksburg, 1925 (Box 160)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1925 (Box 160)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1925 (Box 160)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1925 (Box 160)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1925 (Box 160)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1925 (Box 160)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1925 (Box 160)
    - Roanoke, 1925 (Box 160)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1925 (Box 160)
    - Roaring Fork, 1925 (Box 161)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1925 (Box 161)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1925 (Box 161)
    - Southeastern Express Company, 1925 (Box 161)
    - Southern, 1925 (Box 161)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1925 (Box 161)
    - Tazewell Street, 1925 (Box 161)
    - Valley, 1925 (Box 161)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1925 (Box 161)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1925 (Box 162)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1925 (Box 162)
    - Virginian, 1925 (Box 162)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1925 (Box 162)
    - Virginia Southern, 1925 (Box 162)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1925 (Box 162)
    - Washington - Virginia, 1925 (Box 162)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1925 (Box 162)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1925 (Box 162)
    - Winchester and Western, 1925 (Box 162)
  - 1926.
    - American Railway Express Company, 1926 (Box 163)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1926 (Box 163)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1926 (Box 163)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1926 (Box 163)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1926 (Box 163)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1926 (Box 163)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1926 (Box 163)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1926 (Box 163)
    - Clinchfield, 1926 (Box 164)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg (2 folders), 1926 (Box 164)
    - Danville and Western, 1926 (Box 164)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1926 (Box 164)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1926 (Box 164)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1926 (Box 164)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1926 (Box 164)
    - Interstate, 1926 (Box 164)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1926 (Box 165)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1926 (Box 165)
    - Marion and Rye Valley (2 folders), 1926 (Box 165)